<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Booki</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="teststrings">"He smiled understandingly — much more than understandingly. It was one of those rare smiles with a quality of eternal reassurance in it, that you may come across four or five times in life. It faced — or seemed to face — the whole eternal world for an instant, and then concentrated on you with an irresistible prejudice in your favor. It understood you just as far as you wanted to be understood, believed in you as you would like to believe in yourself, and assured you that it had precisely the impression of you that, at your best, you hoped to convey."

— F. Scott Fitzgerald, "The Great Gatsby"</string>

    <string name="teststring2">
        In a quaint village nestled amidst rolling hills, lived a curious boy named Oliver. One summer afternoon, while wandering through the forest, he stumbled upon a hidden glade. There, he met a peculiar creature—a whimsical sprite with shimmering wings named Aurora. With her mischievous grin, Aurora led Oliver on an adventure beyond his wildest dreams. Together, they danced among the fireflies and whispered secrets to the ancient trees. As twilight enveloped the land, Oliver realized he had ventured farther than ever before. With a twinkle in her eye, Aurora bid him farewell, leaving him with memories that would forever ignite his imagination. And so, Oliver returned home, but the magic of that enchanted glade lingered in his heart, a treasure to cherish in the quiet moments of his days.</string>
    <string name="teststring3"> Deep in the heart of the bustling city, amidst the cacophony of sounds and flurry of activity, there was a forgotten bookstore. Tucked away on a nondescript street, its shelves held treasures beyond compare. One rainy afternoon, a weary traveler named Emily stumbled upon its weathered façade. Intrigued, she stepped inside, where the musty scent of old books enveloped her. Amidst the stacks, she discovered a leather-bound tome, its pages whispering secrets of forgotten realms. Lost in its enchanting prose, Emily was transported to distant lands and forgotten times. As she emerged from the depths of the story, she realized that sometimes, the greatest adventures are found in the quiet corners of the world, waiting patiently to be discovered by those with open hearts and curious minds.    <string name="teststring4">In a quaint village nestled amidst rolling hills, lived a curious boy named Oliver. One summer afternoon, while wandering through the forest, he stumbled upon a hidden glade. There, he met a peculiar creature—a whimsical sprite with shimmering wings named Aurora. With her mischievous grin, Aurora led Oliver on an adventure beyond his wildest dreams. Together, they danced among the fireflies and whispered secrets to the ancient trees. As twilight enveloped the land, Oliver realized he had ventured farther than ever before. With a twinkle in her eye, Aurora bid him farewell, leaving him with memories that would forever ignite his imagination. And so, Oliver returned home, but the magic of that enchanted glade lingered in his heart, a treasure to cherish in the quiet moments of his days.</string>
    </string>
</resources>